

Jyoti Ghanghoriya

Software Engineer

I am an experienced Software Engineer with 4+ years of experience, I have a strong background in software development, system administration, and automation. I am a highly motivated and hardworking individual with a deep passion for Innovation and growth. I have a deep understanding of SDLC, infrastructure as code, continuous integration, delivery, and containerization. Additionally, I have strong communication and collaboration skills which makes me an amazing team player.

ghanghoriya.jyoti@gmail.com

iyotighanghoriya.github.io/

github.com/jyotighanghoriya

+919630921878

in linkedin.com/in/jyoti-ghanghoriya-006388ab

leetcode.com/user5367Qc/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Developer SAP Labs India

09/2023 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Developed Golang operators to automate the seamless provisioning process for BTP tenants in a unified manner resulting in a 90% reduction in provisioning time
- Led the setup of end-to-end pipelines and development clusters for operators, ensuring smooth and efficient CICD processes by reducing 90% of CICD time.
- Implemented validation webhooks in Golang to assess the behaviour of resources before executing business logic which improves reliability by reducing 80% of potential issues.
- Automated Hana license renewal process using java and shell script which reduces 95% of manual effort.

DevOps Engineer SAP Labs India

07/2020 - 08/2023

Achievements/Tasks

- Designed and Deployed an Observability stack with Kafka, Fluent Bit, Event Exporter, Logstash, and OpenSearch in engineering environments, leading to a significant 40% reduction in Mean Time to Resolution (MTTR)
- Implemented Infrastructure automation for one-click automation project, including Consul, Vault, Apigee setup, etc., capable of building the entire cluster with microservices in less than one hour
- Deployed an end-to-end SuccessFactors mobile application to kubernetes and automated the entire release process.
- Developed a framework capable of automatically validating end-to-end OS patching for various SuccessFactors modules using Jenkins, Shell script, and Python, thereby reducing manual effort by 70%.

Software Developer Intern SAP Labs India

01/2020 - 07/2020

Bangalore,India

Achievements/Tasks

 Developed a framework capable of performing automatic end-to-end testing for existing bots using Node.js, Python, RobotFramework, and the Selenium Library, thereby reducing manual testing time by 95%.

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Received the Star Performer Award for contributions to the OCA and Bot Readability Platform project.

Volunteered at Code Unnati for career counselling of college students.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Learning Summary Prior Representation for Extractive Summarization (06/2019 - 12/2019)

 Successfully implemented project on extractive summarization to generate effective summaries on DUC Dataset with ROUGE-1 and ROUGE-2 Score as 35.57 and 10.07.

Classroom Attendance System Using Face Recognition (07/2017 - 04/2019)

 Successfully implemented project on classroom attendance system which can recognize face of student and mark the attendance on the server upon the successful verification of identity.

Food Ordering System (07/2017 - 12/2017)

Created Food Ordering website using Bootstrap, JAVA, MYSQL DB

CERTIFICATES

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (05/2021 - Present) (05/2021 - Present)

https://www.credly.com/badges/16ed1ecb-a69b-4426-aad3f3593eb69306

WORK EXPERIENCE

Summer Intern

National Institute of Technology, Tiruchirappalli

04/2019 - 06/2019,

Tiruchirappalli, India

Achievements/Tasks

- Successfully implemented project on "Event Based Extractive Summarization based on Event Semantic Relevance from External Linguistic Resources"
- Used DUC 2001 Dataset and Verbocean as external linguistic resource to find out the similarity between words.

Contact: Dr. S Jaya Nirmala (Assistant Professor, Dept of CSE)

EDUCATION

M.Tech(CSE)

NIT, Tiruchirappalli

07/2018 - 05/2020,

8.04

B.E.

SGSITS, Indore

07/2014 - 06/2018, 6.496

Sant Meera

Ujjain, M.P.

07/2013 - 07/2014, 84%

Sant Meera

Ujjain, M.P.

07/2011 - 04/2012, 89.33%

AREA OF INTEREST

DSA
OS
Networks
DBMS

ORGANIZATIONS

SAP Labs India (01/2020 - Present)

Software Developer Intern(First six months), Associated DevOps Engineer, DevOps Engineer (Present)

LANGUAGES

English Hindi
Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

chess Travelling Fitness

Professional Development Activities

Volunteering Activities | Competitive Programming

Problem Solving